Mustafa Çetinkaya

Istanbul, Turkey

mucet90@gmail.com



+90 546 815 99 28



linkedin.com/in/mucet



https://mucet.github.io/

Summary

MSc.

Senior Software Engineer with +5 years of experience.

Experienced in .Net Core, .Net Web API, WPF, xUnit, T-SQL, and jQuery.

Skilled in working on DDD, TDD, and n-Tier Architecture.

Skilled in working on Agile Methodologies and BitBucket with Jira.

Experienced in working on Mobile and Computer Forensics (over 150 cases investigated).

Experience



🐚 Senior Software Engineer

Istanbul University-Cerrahpasa

Aug 2022 - Present (4 months +)



Research And Development Manager

Adli Tip Kurumu (Council of Forensic Medicine)

Apr 2019 - Jul 2022 (3 years 4 months)

Laboratory Management System

The application was created with Claris Filemaker and is run on the server side. The process of entry, management, and reporting of the information regarding the evidence in the cases is carried out on this system. Experts are classified according to their powers. The application works with different database systems.

Console Apps

Console applications have been developed to automate some analyzes by communicating with different servers via Curl.

Desktop Apps

Desktop applications have been developed that allow some analysis to be automated. Application distribution was done with ClickOnce.

Web Apps

Web applications have been developed using ASP.Net Core technology, which automates some analysis.

Windows Services

Windows Service applications have been developed that enable virtual machines to perform the tasks assigned to them in a sequential manner.

Mobile Forensic Examiner

Adli Tıp Kurumu (Council of Forensic Medicine)

Apr 2017 - Apr 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Mobile devices belonging to terrorist crimes cases and other pieces of evidence (memory card, sim card, etc.) obtained from these devices were examined.

The tools used: Access Data FTK Imager, Cellebrite UFED 4PC, Cellebrite UFED PA, MSAB XRY, Oxygen Forensic, Forensic Explorer, X-Ways Forensics, Magnet Axiom, Passware Kit Forensic.

Software Developer

Maxinn Kurumsal Hizmetler

Sep 2012 - Sep 2014 (2 years 1 month)

It is a project that allows users to purchase services/products on the website, earn points with purchases made, and use the earned points for their next shopping. In the project, RFID cards were given to the users and user identification was carried out on these cards.

Web App

An e-commerce web application was developed using ASP.Net MVC technology, which enables users to purchase products through the website. The app also has an admin panel.

Technologies used: ASP.Net MVC, Jquery, MSSQL, TFS.

Desktop App

A desktop application has been developed that enables the realization of sales transactions in workplaces. The distribution of the application was carried out with ClickOnce.

Technologies used: WPF, MSSQL, TFS.

Education

Istanbul University

Master's degree, Computer Science

2019 - 2021

Thesis topic: Malware Detection With Memory Analysis on Windows System Processes

Istanbul University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2014 - 2016

Suleyman Demirel University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Teacher Education 2008 - 2013

Center of Vocational and Technical Education

High School's degree, Computer Programming 2005 - 2008

Licenses & Certifications

- MIT University Entrepreneurship Certificate Massachusetts Institute of Technology
- SDU Foreign Language Certificate Suleyman Demirel University
- Forensic Explorer Analyst GetData Forensics
- Certified BlackLight Examiner BlackBag Technologies
- in Building Web APIs with ASP.NET Core in .NET 6 LinkedIn
- Advanced Web APIs with ASP.NET Core in .NET 6 LinkedIn
- in .NET MAUI First Look LinkedIn
- in Advanced ASP.NET Core: Unit Testing LinkedIn
- C# Test-Driven Development LinkedIn
- in C# Refactoring Tips and Tricks LinkedIn
- in Learning Vue.js LinkedIn

Skills

C# • SQL • JavaScript • .NET Core • API Development • Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF)
• Unit Testing • Git • Agile Methodologies • Scrum

Honors & Awards

Volunteering - İbrahim Özaydın Mesleki ve Teknik Anadolu Lisesi

Digital Forensics were explained to the students of İbrahim Özaydın Mesleki ve Teknik Anadolu High School.